# Chris Kankiewicz

12231 N 19<sup>th</sup> Street #264 Phoenix, Arizona 85022 Cell: 602-684-0523

Email: Chris@ChrisKankiewicz.com

AIM: ChrisKankiewicz

Website: www.ChrisKankiewicz.com

### Summary

Self taught web designer and programmer with real world experience and a desire to learn. Personal strengths include advanced troubleshooting and problem solving skills, the capacity to acquire and apply new knowledge guickly and great customer service skills.

### **Experience**

## **PetSmart Store Support Group**

Solution Center Technician (February 2008 - Present)

Provided over-the-phone technical support to store and corporate employees.

Performed advanced troubleshooting on store servers, registers, and workstations.

### Jannenga Enterprises, LLC

Web & Graphics Designer (May 2006 - October 2007)

Conceptualized, designed and coordinated the implementation of detailed web pages and graphics.

Performed routine and advanced maintenance on PC systems, basic and advanced networks, and other digital equipment.

#### **Elontec**

Systems Technician (October 2007 - February 2008)

Planned and implemented store-wide PC and Point of Sale systems and performed server upgrades.

Performed basic troubleshooting on implemented systems.

### **Best Buy Co.**

In-Store PC Technician (April 2005 - July 2006)

Performed routine maintenance on PC systems and other digital equipment

Opened, operated, and closed Geek Squad department and provided customer service as needed.

### Qualifications

#### Proficient with:

- PHP
- (X)HTML
- CSS
- Search Engine Optimization
- Photoshop CS3
- Eclipse IDE
- · All Windows operating systems
- All Microsoft Office applications
- WordPress

# Familiar with or learning:

- JavaScript
- Drupal CMS
- · LAMP environments
- MySQL
- Zend IDE
- Java
- Unix/Linux based operating systems
- · Cisco IOS
- Remedy Action Request System

### **Education**

### **DeVry University**

July 2005 - February 2008

 Bachelor's of Science Degree in Network and Communication Management

### **Shadow Mountain High School**

2001 - 2005

- High school diploma
- National Honor Society

# **Achievements**

- · Eagle Scout
- Project: CK-Gallery (http://code.web-geek.net/ck-gallery)
- Attended Defcon Security Convention 2005 2008